Guide to the Photographs by and relating to Allen Ginsberg MSS.PHOTO.0450
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Contact Sheets, Series 2
  - Contact sheet 372, 1985 May 31; 372 (Item 11)
    New York City; Andre Vosnesensky in elevator Hilton Hotel 6th Ave. NYC; Harry Smith's room paintings and books; Francis Lee (filmmaker) and Esther Rattner (gentile) sculptor at Julian Beck's birthday party; Julian Beck remission from cancer
  - Contact sheet 373, 1985 June 2; 373 (Item 11)
    "New York City; Belmar, NJ; Garden City, NY; Hilton Hotel 6th Ave. NYC; kitchen window; Kerry Katsouras marriage, Garden City Greek Orthodox Church"
  - Contact sheet 374, 1985 June 9; 374 (Item 11)
    "W. Orange, NJ; Clara in St. Barnaby Hospital"
  - Contact sheet 375, 1985 June 9; 375 (Item 11)
    "W. Orange, NJ; New York City"
  - Contact sheet 376, 1985 June 9; 376 (Item 11)
    "W. Orange, NJ"
  - Contact sheet 377, 1985 June 9; 377 (Item 11)
    "Garden City, New York City"
  - Contact sheet 378, 1985 June 16; 378 (Item 11)
  - Contact sheet 379, 1985 June 17; 379 (Item 11)
    New York City; altar (shrine) 437 E. 12th St.; graduation day
    Joel Gaidemak
  - Contact sheet 380, 1985 June 17; 380 (Item 11)
    New York City; kitchen window; Indian poets; Brooklyn Bridge; Tompkins Square
  - Contact sheet 381, 1985 June 20; 381 (Item 11)
    "Orono, ME; Ezra Pound conference"
  - Contact sheet 382, 1985 June 20; 382 (Item 11)
  - Contact sheet 383, 1985 June 20; 383 (Item 11)
    "New York City; Orono, ME; Ezra Pound conference"
  - Contact sheet 384, 1985 June 21; 384 (Item 11)
    "New York City; Orono, ME; Allen Ginsberg self-portraits"
  - Contact sheet 385, 1985 June 22; 385 (Item 11)
    "Orono, ME; Robert Creeley and children with canoe; "
  - Contact sheet 386, 1985 June 23; 386 (Item 11)
    "Orono, ME; Robert Creeley at Berenice Abbott's lodge "
  - Contact sheet 387, 1985 June 24; 387 (Item 11)
    "Orono, ME; Robert Creeley at Berenice Abbott's lodge"
  - Contact sheet 388, 1985 June 30; 388 (Item 11)
    "Paterson, NJ; New York City; Lyle Brooks' wedding"
  - Contact sheet 389, 1985 July 1; 389 (Item 11)
    NYC?
    Happy Traum wife; Penny and Ro
  - Contact sheet 390, 1985 July 4; 390 (Item 11)
    "New York City; Southampton, NY; Fireworks from roof of 437 E. 12th St."
    Susan Soros; Dorothy Norman
  - Contact sheet 391, 1985 July 6; 391 (Item 11)
    "New York City; Southampton, Easthampton, NY; Lucien Carr at Robert Frank show; Bob Rosenthal in office; taxi views; Grumin House Nicaraguan Relief Benefit"
  - Contact sheet 392, 1985 July 7; 392 (Item 11)
    "Southampton, Easthampton, NY"
  - Contact sheet 393, 1985 July 7; 393 (Item 11)
    "Southampton, Easthampton, NY; New York City; site of Paradise Alley; fireworks"
  - Contact sheet 394, 1985 July 13; 394 (Item 11)
    "New York City; Francesco Clemente, Petersburg Press, drawing my picture"
    Clemente, Francesco
  - Contact sheet 395, 1985 July 13; 395 (Item 11)
    "New York City; Francesco Clemente drawing me photoing him, Petersburg Press"
  - Contact sheet 396, 1985 July 13; 396 (Item 11)
    "New York City; Garden City, NY; Francesco Clemente at Kiev and at Petersburg Press; on way 2nd Ave. winos (near 8th-9th St.); Harry Smith at home, his door room, Brooks Wedding"
  - Contact sheet 397, 1985 July 13; 397 (Item 11)
    "Garden City, NY; Lyle Brooks and Kerry Katsouris Wedding (July 13), Garden City Greek Orthodox Church"
  - Contact sheet 398, 1985 July 13; 398 (Item 11)
  - Contact sheet 399, 1985 July 13; 399 (Item 11)
    "Garden City, NY; Boulder, CO; Lyle Brooks and Kerry Katsouris Wedding (July 13), Garden City Greek Orthodox Church"
  - Contact sheet 400, 1985 July 13; 400 (Item 11)
    "Garden City, NY; Boulder, CO; Lyle Brooks and Kerry Katsouris Wedding (July 13), Garden City Greek Orthodox Church; lunch at Padwas"
  - Contact sheet 401, 1985 July 16; 401 (Item 12)
    "Southampton, NY; New York City"
  - Contact sheet 402, 1985 July 22; 402 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, CO; Varsity Townhouse, room 222"
  - Contact sheet 403, 1985 July 23; 403 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 404, 1985 July 29; 404 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 405, 1985 July 29; 405 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, CO; Naropa students"
  - Contact sheet 406, 1985 July 29; 406 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 407, 1985 July 29; 407 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 408, 1985 July 29; 408 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 409, 1985 July 29; 409 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 410, 1985 July 29; 410 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 411, 1985 July 29; 411 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 412, 1985 July 29; 412 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, CO; Allen Ginsberg self-portraits"
  - Contact sheet 413, 1985 July 29; 413 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 414, 1985 July 29; 414 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 415, 1985 July 29; 415 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 416, 1985 July 29; 416 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 417, 1985 July 29; 417 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 418, 1985 Aug. 1; 418 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, CO; Allen Ginsberg self-portrait"
  - Contact sheet 419, 1985 Aug. 1; 419 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 420, 1985 Aug. 1; 420 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 421, 1985 Aug. 1; 421 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 422, 1985 Aug. 1; 422 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 423, 1985 Aug. 1; 423 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 424, 1985 Aug. 3; 424 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 425, 1985 Aug. 3; 425 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 426, 1985 Aug. 5; 426 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 427, 1985 Aug. 5; 427 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 428, 1985 Aug. 5; 428 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, CO; Corso in dean's office before reading; Allen Ginsberg self-portrait"
  - Contact sheet 429, 1985 Aug. 6; 429 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, CO; Padwa garden supper-lunch"
  - Contact sheet 430, 1985 Aug. 8; 430 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, Denver, CO; Four Mile House"
  - Contact sheet 431, 1985 Aug. 13; 431 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, Denver, CO; Peter Hale, 1:30 AM, 1001 Mapleton; house at 4 Mile Historic Park, Denver restored by Ed White - near "4 Mile House"; Nanao Sakaki; Jamgon Kongtrul; Ed White at 461 Humboldt St. Denver, Carla Coleman Residence Museum; Humboldt St. Historic District Denver 1075 Humboldt"
  - Contact sheet 432, 1985 Aug. 15; 432 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, CO; San Francisco, CA; Peter Hale at Faigao's, Sierra pix in photo store S.F."
    Hale, Peter
  - Contact sheet 433, 1985 Aug. 19; 433 (Item 12)
    "San Francisco, CA; Party after "Sexuality and Spirituality"
  - Contact sheet 434, 1985 Aug. 21; 434 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 435, 1985 Aug. 15; 435 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 436, 1985 Aug. 15; 436 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 437, 1985 Aug. 16; 437 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, CO; Jerry Aronson and filmmaker"
    Aronson, Jerry
  - Contact sheet 438, 1985 Aug. 19; 438 (Item 12)
    "Berkeley, CA; San Francisco, CA"
  - Contact sheet 439, 1985 Aug. 30; 439 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 440, 1985 Aug. 31; 440 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, CO; Rocky Mountain Dharma Center"
  - Contact sheet 441, 1985 Sept. 5; 441 (Item 12)
    Rocky Mountain Dharma Center; Chogyam Trungpa Rinpoche
  - Contact sheet 442, 1985 Sept. 6; 442 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 443, 1985 Sept. 9; 443 (Item 12)
    "COLOR: Boulder, CO; Rocky Mountain Dharma Center"
  - Contact sheet 444, 1985 Sept. 10; 444 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 445, 1985 Sept. 10; 445 (Item 12)
    "Boulder, CO; Long Island, NY; Rocky Mountain Dharma Center"
  - Contact sheet 446, 1985 Sept. 15; 446 (Item 12)
    "Long Island, NY"
    Wilem De Kooning; Elaine De Ko
  - Contact sheet 447, 1985 Sept. 15; 447 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 448, 1985 Aug. 9; 448 (Item 12)
    "COLOR: Long Island, NY"
  - Contact sheet 449, 1985 Sept. 13; 449 (Item 12)
    New York City; funeral outside 437 E. 12th St.; Paradise Alley vacant lot
    Steven Taylor
  - Contact sheet 450, 1985 Sept. 16; 450 (Item 12)
    "Long Island?, NY"
  - Contact sheet 451, 1985 Sept. 17; 451 (Item 12)
    Larry Rivers with wife and bab
  - Contact sheet 452, 1985 Sept. 22; 452 (Item 12)
    NJ?
  - Contact sheet 453, 1985 Sept. 22; 453 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 454, 1985 Sept. 19; 454 (Item 12)
    "Long Island?, NY; New York City; Julian Beck's funeral"
  - Contact sheet 455, 1985 Sept. 19; 455 (Item 12)
    "Long Island?, NY; Julian Beck's funeral"
    Larry Rivers
  - Contact sheet 456, 1985 Sept. 20; 456 (Item 12)
    "Long Island?, NY; Julian Beck's funeral; car crash"
  - Contact sheet 457, 1985 Sept. 20; 457 (Item 12)
    New York City; PEN club
  - Contact sheet 458, 1985 Sept. 20; 458 (Item 12)
    New York City; street scenes; gallery
    Alex Katz
  - Contact sheet 459, 1985 Sept. 24; 459 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 460, 1985 Sept. 24; 460 (Item 12)
    New York City; kitchen window view from 437 E. 12th St.
  - Contact sheet 461, 1985 Sept. 24; 461 (Item 12)
    New York City; kitchen window view from 437 E. 12th St.; Allen Ginsberg self-portrait
  - Contact sheet 462, 1985 Sept. 27; 462 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 463, 1985 Sept. 29; 463 (Item 12)
    COLOR: New York City; fishing
  - Contact sheet 464, 1985 Sept. 29; 464 (Item 12)
    New York City; fishing; Mary Help of Christians R.C. Church
  - Contact sheet 465, 1985 Sept. 29; 465 (Item 12)
    New York City; Mary Help of Christians R.C. Church; Alex Katz painting my portrait; Greg Ruggero of Union College
  - Contact sheet 466, 1985 Oct. 3; 466 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 467, 1985 Oct. 3; 467 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 468, 1985 Oct. 3; 468 (Item 12)
    New York City; John Wieners in Christine's restaurant; Norman Mailer chairman at PEN Club meeting; Carl Solomon and Ted Morgan fishing in Bronx
  - Contact sheet 469, 1985 Oct. 5; 469 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 470, 1985 Oct. 7; 470 (Item 12)
  - Contact sheet 471, 1985 Oct. 7; 471 (Item 12)
    New York City; Italian NYU professor in Veselka's back room
  - Contact sheet 472, 1985 Oct. 8; 472 (Item 12)
    New York City; Alice Notley reading
  - Contact sheet 473, 1985 Oct. 8; 473 (Item 12)
    "New York City; Washington, DC; Charlottesville, VA; Monticello-teacher in school; bar in Charlottesville; Lucien Carr in DC; Sid Kaplan in NY; Chinese Restaurant Bowery; self-portrait"
  - Contact sheet 474, 1985 Oct. 10; 474 (Item 12)
    "New York City; Washington, DC; Charlottesville, VA; Allen Ginsberg self-portrait; Human Rights Defense Fun banquet Waldorf Hotel; mirror in Monticello"
  - Contact sheet 475, 1985 Oct. 10; 475 (Item 12)
    "New York City; Charlottesville, VA; Allen Ginsberg self-portrait"
  - Contact sheet 476, 1985 Oct. 19; 476 (Item 13)
    "New York City; Baltimore, MD; Washington, DC; Sid Kaplan in Chinese vegetarian restaurant; Ted Fields birthday party; Allen Ginsberg self-portrait"
  - Contact sheet 477, 1985 Oct. 25; 477 (Item 13)
    "New York City; Baltimore, MD; Washington, DC; Julian Beck Subohate Ceremony service; altar at 437 E. 12th St.; contracts"
  - Contact sheet 478, 1985 Oct. 25; 478 (Item 13)
    New York City; Julian Beck Suhovate Ceremony service for Hanon and Judith Malina; altar at 437 E. 12th St.; contracts
  - Contact sheet 479, 1985 Oct. 27; 479 (Item 13)
    New York City; Josef Brodsky at cafe on McDougal St.; William Burroughs party at Mary Boone gallery
  - Contact sheet 480, 1985 Nov. 3; 480 (Item 13)
  - Contact sheet 481, 1985 Nov. 4; 481 (Item 13)
    "New York City; Washington, DC; VA Oyster Shucking Championship"
  - Contact sheet 482, 1985 Nov. 4; 482 (Item 13)
    Kesey, Ken
  - Contact sheet 483, 1985 Nov. 5; 483 (Item 13)
    "New York City; Mary Boone Gallery, party for William Burroughs' Queer; Dinner restaurant after; Burroughs in Bunker, 222 Bowery; my bedroom bed and bookshelf 437 E. 12th St., Apt. 23"
  - Contact sheet 484, 1985 Nov. 15; 484 (Item 13)
    "New York City; Bunker; home with bathroom mirror, new Olympus OM self portrait "
  - Contact sheet 485, 1985 Nov. 11; 485 (Item 13)
    "New York City; Arnold Newman, 437 E. 12th St., living room, loading"
    Arnold Newman
  - Contact sheet 486, 1985 Nov. 14; 486 (Item 13)
  - Contact sheet 487, 1985 Nov. 15; 487 (Item 13)
    "New York City; Copenhagen, Denmark; Moscow, USSR; OM Olympus; NYC departure, club lunch; street limosines distant skyscrapers (Chrysler Bldg); airport video interviews; Vilnius (what) self-portrait; Hotel Drauvgesta (or mush?) self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 488, 1985 Nov. 16; 488 (Item 13)
    "Copenhagen, Denmark; Moscow, USSR; XA; Copenhagen airport and Hotel Royal elevator; #1-3 Jerry Lawrence, Norman Cousins and group (Gass) in rear; #4-18 William Gass, Arthur Miller, Allen Ginsberg, elevator mirror; #19-21 Moscow Airport arrival; (Nov. 17) Arthur Miller and Yevtuchencko; #24-26 Yevtuchenko translating his essay on AG aloud to Inge Morath and AG; #30-35 Banquet Hotel in Moscow outskirts listening to speeches (by Sagatelean or Fedorenko) left to right -?Arthur Miller, Zassourski, Inge Morath, Yevgeny Yevtuchenko, Michael Douskoy interpreter and William Gaddis in rear, Frieda Lurie peeping out next to Gaddis, Zualnowa ladies foreground and Jerry Lawrence of Hollywood; #35 Yevtuchenko speaking"
  - Contact sheet 489, 1985 Nov. 18; 489 (Item 13)
    "Moscow, USSR; Moscow to Vilnus; Yevgeny Yevtuchenko and group; Allen Ginsberg self-portrait"
  - Contact sheet 490, 1985 Nov. 22; 490 (Item 13)
    "Vilnius, USSR; street scenes; group"
  - Contact sheet 491, 1985 Nov. 22; 491 (Item 13)
    "Vilnius, USSR; New York City; #1-2 (Nov. 22) downtown Vilnius journalist, Alex Federas; #6 Arthur Miller; #8-14 self-portrait hotel Dravgesta, room 604, Vilnius, Lithuania; #15 Inge Morath and Arhur Miller doorway Hotel Davgesta; #16-17 self-portraits; #18-24 Studio 20 Vorovsky Str, left Nadezeda Prigov, Bela Achmadulina, Yevgeny Rein, Boris Mreasurer (Bela's hubby), Dmitri Prigoff; #25-26 NYC (Dec. 20-30)?; Gregory Corso New Years' Eve; #31 John Winers and Corso; #32 Brian Graham; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 492, 1985 Nov. 22; 492 (Item 13)
    "Vilnius, USSR; US Writer's Conference #1 Nicolai Federenko and Norman Cousins, head table, right, Salisbury, Gregory Bahlanov; Yassin Zassoursky, Meyulaitis; #3 entrance Napoleonic Hq. meeting room, Inge Morath and Adde Auchincloss with cameras, bearded interpreter Nicolai Moikin, rear Muriel Murphy, William Gaddis, Louis Auchincloss, and with beret KGB's Tavered G. Golenpolsky; #4-6 Michael Sagatetian of Moscow Writers Union, Albertas Laurin Cuckas Ed Tiesa, Arthur Miller, Ivan Drach (Ukraine, poet, long hair) David Kogeltinov, Ghingiz Aitmatov, Jerry Lawrence, Alfonsis Maldonis (Chairman Lithuanian Writers Union) Norvel Young, Interpreter's rear, Nudai Federenko, right Lithuanian writers/observers, rear; #7-8 William Gaddis, Mezulaitis, Auchincloss; #9 same as 4-6 + Charles Fuller, left; #12-14 as 7-8 + Nicolas Slutskis (poet, Jewish); #15-19 Inge Morath and Arthur Miller, Hotel Dravgesta dining room, Vilius; #20-21 Norman Cousins and Federenko; #24 as above 4-6; 25 as above and Isabela Zorina Lithuanian writers/observers, rear; #26-28 observers: Helen Young, Mrs. Salisbury, interpreter Svetlova Makurenkova, Muriel Murphy, Adele Auchincloss, Morn Gass, ?, Inge Morath +?,; #30-31 folk group concluding sessions; 32 Vilnius centrum, Miller and Auchincloss"
  - Contact sheet 493, 1985 Nov. 23; 493 (Item 13)
    "Vilnius, USSR; group, street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 494, 1985 Nov. 25; 494 (Item 13)
    "Minsk, USSR; group; circus"
    Arthur Miller
  - Contact sheet 495, 1985 Nov. 25; 495 (Item 13)
    "Minsk, USSR; 1-6 Writers' Union Banquet speeches; 11-13 Minsk Hotel cousulations clockwise from left Charles Fuller, ?, Michael Sagatelean, Minsk writer's Union head or secty (Nil Gilevich?), Tankred G. Golenpolsky, Tanya Neyatrulofshaya interpreter, Michel Douskoy; interpreter, Nowell Young, Inge Morath camera, Arthur Miller and Jerry Lawrence seated back to camera (11-12) and Auchincloss; #13 same, Dimitri Urnoff, Mary Gass and William Gass from rear with above group; 14-21 Hatayn memorial cemetary to villages Nazis destroyed, outside of Minsk; 17-18 Inge Morath; 19 Adele Auchincloss? 20 Russians on the path; 22-27 "Great Patriotic War" Partisan Museum Muriel Murphy, Gass, Miller, Auchincloss, Tanya and guide Nil and Gelevich and Urnoff; 32 Norvel Young"
  - Contact sheet 496, 1985 Nov. 28; 496 (Item 13)
    "Vilnius, Moscow, USSR; 1A-2 Theater in Vilnius Prismani Pirismani Play; 3-4 Inge Morath and Arthur Miller and Dimitri? Urinoff Urnov (Nov. 24) Vilnius Drovegesta Hotel leaving for Minsk; 6-11 Minsk Writer's Union meeting; 7 Michael Sagatelian, Charles Fuller, Tanya Nezabutofskay interpreter, Louis Auchincloss, Jerry Lawrence, Norvell Young, Muriel Murphy, Dimitri Urnoff and Minsk Writers' Union members; 15-18 Moscow Writer's Union Main Dining Room; (Nov. 27) 16-18 Muriel Murphy with William Gaddis and Tanya (18); 19 Academy of Sciences, Alexander S. Molyarchik Norvel Young, (yelled at) William Gass, William Gaddis; 20-26 Moscow State Lomonosou University Prof. Vassen N. Zassowski's Conference of Specialists in US-English Literature Teachers from all over Soviet Union, audience for our readings and speeches Nov. 29 at 2 pm (thereabouts) "All-Union Conference of Speicalists in American Literature"; #27-35 Foreign Lit Mag - "Foreign Lit. Monthly" Nov. 28, 1985 Oleg S. Vasiliev, Dept. Ed. Georgii P. Zlobin Editor Adele Auchincloss, of Western Fiction; 28 Norvel Young, Michael Douskoy, Jerry Lawrence, Bill Gass, William Gaddis; 31 Muriel Murphy and Isabella Zorina and Taterna Lavina Poetry Editor and Andrei Sergeiv with beard and glasses"
  - Contact sheet 497, 1985 Nov. 29; 497 (Item 13)
    "Moscow, USSR; street scenes; group; Allen Ginsberg self-portrait"
  - Contact sheet 498, 1985 Nov. 30; 498 (Item 13)
    "Moscow, Leningrad, USSR; 1A Moscow Foreign Lit. Monthly meeting (earlier); Leningrad, Admiralty and Hermitage; 2-3 William Gaddis, With Hermitage and Neva; 4 Adele and Louis Auchincloss; Allen Ginsberg Neva Hermitage; 6 Gaddis, Dmitri Ornoff; 7A William Gass; 11-14 Auchincloss and Hermitage; 18-19 William Gass; 20-22 Auchincloss; 28-31 meeting at Writers' Union; 33A Leningrad Hotel hall ground floor; 34 Gaddis, Frieda Lurie, M. Douskoi entering Hermitage"
  - Contact sheet 499, 1985 Nov. 30; 499 (Item 13)
    "Leningrad, USSR; street scenes; subway"
  - Contact sheet 500, 1985 Nov. 30; 500 (Item 13)
    "Leningrad, USSR; Louis Auchinclose in Dostoevsky's house"
    Louis Auchinclose
  - Contact sheet 501, 1985 Dec. 1; 501 (Item 13)
    "Leningrad, USSR; Writers' Union Foreign Secty; Allen Ginsberg, self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 502, 1985 Dec. 2; 502 (Item 13)
    "Moscow, USSR; Red Square; group; Louis Auchincloss; Allen Ginsberg; 1-4 Moscow Writer's Union Restaurant - departure day from Moscow, lunch 1-3 pm, William Gaddis, Svetlana Makweakova (interpreter) Dimitri Urnoff (Gorki Inst. American Studies) and Mary Gass (R.); 5 Adele and Louis Auchincloss, Nelly Kopnina (interpreter); 6-10 General view (as above) Muriel Murphy, Mary Gass, Frieda Lurie (standing bending over Mary Gass) Ruth Oxenberg (friend of Muriel); 11-14 Auchincloss (Adele Louis) and Gass (William and Mary) couples and Tanya (interpreter) depart Moscow airport; 15-21 Ylena Bonner and press crowd, departing Moscow, going thru customs and passport exam, TV cameras, officials, etc.; 23-29 Karl Marx statue, snow bearded, Moscow 1 AM, with Andrew Lewis (Yalie) and AG; 30 Red Square 1 AM - Andy Lewis & Allen Ginsberg"
  - Contact sheet 503, 1985 Dec. 4; 503 (Item 13)
    "Tiblist, Msveta, Parajanof, USSR; group"
  - Contact sheet 504, 1985 Dec. 4; 504 (Item 13)
    "Moscow, USSR"
  - Contact sheet 505, 1985 Dec. 7; 505 (Item 13)
    "Tiblist, W. Georgia, USSR; 7 Secretary Georgia Writer's Union (Drakli Abashedze?) Tblisi Hotel entrance; 8-9 Hotel and doorlady Tbilisi; 10-11 Georgia Writer's Union Mansion Tblisi; 11-35 Stalin birth house, Gori, Georgia locomotive, etc. 16-19 museum, mausoleum interiors; 23 toilets; 26-32 birth cabin/house; 28 W. Prof Menashvilli, same; 29 w/Michael Douskoy, same; 36 auto wreck return trip to Tiblisi from Vani; 1A-6 (12/4/85) Party Moscow after Alex Kozloff's jazz rock New Wave arsenal concert Georgian (?) singers"
  - Contact sheet 506, 1985 Dec. 8; 506 (Item 13)
    "Vanni, Georgia, USSR; Banquet in Vani, West Georgia, for Tiziano Tabillze Museum; #11 Simon Chichevadze's house 6:30 pm on at table Revay Gnanishville; Prof. Menashvilli 313 center +14 and Poetest Taoist leader Ta-ma-da also Herakli Abashidze, the Georgian Writers' Union Pres.; Ilja Kutich; Michael Douskoy translator; Allen Ginsberg"
  - Contact sheet 507, 1985 Dec. 9; 507 (Item 13)
    "Tiblisi, USSR; doctors?; group"
  - Contact sheet 508, 1985 Dec. 9; 508 (Item 13)
    "Tiblist, USSR; Allen Ginsberg; street scenes; markets; Tibilesi, Georgia: 27-30 anti-American posters; 5-9 Lenin Square; last 3 lady street sweeper"
  - Contact sheet 509, 1985 Dec. 10; 509 (Item 13)
    "Tiblist, Paralanof, USSR; group"
  - Contact sheet 510, 1985 Dec. 10; 510 (Item 13)
    "Tiblist, Paralanof, USSR; (Chez) Sergei Parafanoff's house, T'Bilisi, among others - priest Fr. George Aarazeshvilli (22+28) Sergei Parajanoff - 18, 19 etc.; Michael Dousky unhappy interpreter as in 1-8 on right; Alexandre Atanssian (2nd director for parajanoff) as in 26-28 w/beard; Allen Ginsberg"
  - Contact sheet 511, 1985 Dec. 12; 511 (Item 13)
    "Tiblist, Batumi, USSR; Tibilisi - Sergei Parajanoff's house and Alexandre Atansian (asst. director) with painter Albert Dilbarian (Givy") as in 1, 4, 6, 7, 9 black turtleneck; Batumiu Balumeron Black Sea with: AG, Michael Douskoy Moscow interpreter, Irakli Kopuria (Georgian interpreter); translator from Writers' Union of Georgea; 23-24 shoestores; 25 streets, tobacco stores (27); 12-15 hole in which Douskey fell at nite (showing Irakle Topuria) Pastry Shope 28-31; 16 Parajanoffs entrance balcony stairs and gate to house on alley; Bathroom Batumi Hotel; Allen Ginsberg"
  - Contact sheet 512, 1985 Dec. 15; 512 (Item 13)
    "Moscow, USSR; New York City; Peredelkino Dec. 15, 1985 Sunday: 2-10 Yevtuchenko and Meseureb afternoon; 11-20 Vosnesensky's house, rock and roll crew stars 6 pm eveing; 11 Boris Grebenshikoff (w guitar) and Artion Trovitski (critic block group) Stas Maimin (of Flowers then Stars Maimen group) Alex Loeseff; Mrs. Vosnesensky Zoya; older poet singer #10 translator Michael Douskoy; chauffeur in sweater furry; 21-26 NYC Dec. 18-19, 1985; kitchen window snow/Bill Rizzo; 27-30 Vincent Mai's Xmas, Long Island - The Family; 31-34 John Wieners, Gregory Corso, New Year's Eve; Allen Ginsberg; Brian Graham; Eugene Brooks"
  - Contact sheet 513, 1985 Dec. 20; 513 (Item 13)
    "Copenhagen; New York City; returning thru Copenhagen Dec. 16-17, 1985; 1-5 Copenhagen Xmas shopwindows; 6-11 Lotte and Anita Thomson's house; Thomson, Bjorn Bennike; 12-13 Bjorn Bennike Copenhagen Central Square; 16-18 Art opening, Vosnesensky (see other photos with Nina Bores" other contact sheet; Dec. 19, 1985 #23-27 party at Douglas Drinne's Dance Class apartment, W. Broadway across from PEN Club; Dec. 20? AM? 28-30 NY kitchen window; 34-35 Arthur Miller, Connecticut before his fireplace Dec. 21 or 22, 1985; see other photos of Vosnesensy's friend "Nina Bouis"; Allen Ginsberg; self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 514, 1985 Dec. 17; 514 (Item 13)
    "Batumi, USSR; Yesslain's house; markets; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 515, 1985 Dec. 25; 515 (Item 13)
    New York City; Algonquin Hotel NYC; Xmas Mai Brooks house
  - Contact sheet 516, 1985 Dec. 31; 516 (Item 13)